Contact

noxy4b@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nokukhanya-bergh-593425117 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Postman API Software Development MySQL

Certifications

JavaScript

National Certificate: Systems

Development

Nokukhanya Bergh

Junior Developer at Barron: Switch your brand ON South Africa Brakpan, Gauteng, South Africa

Summary

Experienced Junior Software Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the apparel and fashion industry. Skilled in JavaScript, Node.js, Digital Marketing, Jasmine Framework, and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). Strong professional with a national certificate focused in Information Technology (system development) from Umuzi Academy.

Experience

Barron: Switch your brand ON South Africa 1 year 5 months Junior Software Developer March 2022 - Present (6 months)

Software Developer Assistant April 2021 - March 2022 (1 year) Edenvale, Gauteng, South Africa

Umuzi.org Web Developer recruit March 2020 - February 2021 (1 year)

Tastee Creationz founder, Managing Director July 2018 - November 2020 (2 years 5 months) tsakane

Capitec Bank
Service Consultant
May 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 9 months)
Brakpan Area, South Africa

Education

Umuzi Academy

national certificate, Information Technology (system development) · (2020 - 2021)

University of South Africa/Universiteit van Suid-Afrika Higher certificate, Marketing/Marketing Management, General · (2020 - 2020)

Ubuntu business school

Certificate, New venture creations · (2018 - 2018)